nabiscoworld.com 2018-06-23

# Mondelēz International Privacy Policy

Scope

This privacy statement applies to MondelezInternational.com and Mondelēz Global LLC ("Mondelēz Global") websites, services, applications and products that collect data and display these terms (collectively, our "sites" ). it does not apply to mondelēz global sites, services and products that do not display or link to this statement or that have their own privacy statements.

Information We Collect

Mondelēz Global collects many types of information in order to operate effectively and provide you the best products, services and experiences we can. This information includes: 

  * Information you provide (for example, when you register with our sites, sign up for our newsletters or email lists, participate in surveys and purchase our products or services); 
  * Information collected automatically (for example, we may use cookies, pixel tags and similar technologies that collect information about your use of our sites, interactions with our emails, and information about your web browser or device). Please see the full **Cookies and Similar Technologies** section below for more information;
  * Information collected from other sources (for example, we may collect information from commercially available sources such as data aggregators and public databases). 

We may also combine this information to help us tailor our communications and advertisements to you, develop exceptional products and services, and improve our sites.

  * We also use approved third party providers, such as ad networks and analytics providers, to deliver, track and measure advertisements on our sites and third party websites. These providers may use cookies and similar technologies to collect non-identified information (i.e., data that does not identify a specific individual) such as your IP address. They may also use data received from third parties to assist them in delivering more meaningful advertisements to you.

Cookies and Similar Technologies

When you view or interact with our sites, electronic communications, and advertisements, we use cookies, pixel tags and similar technologies to automatically receive certain information about your computer or device and how you engage with our sites and ads. We may also allow approved third party online service providers, such as ad networks and analytics providers, to receive this information. This data is used for many legitimate purposes that help us serve you better. However, you have a variety of tools to control cookies and similar technologies, including: 

  * Web browser controls to block and delete cookies, or adjust your tracking preferences;
  * Visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance's opt-out page [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) or network advertising initiative's opt-out page [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed) to opt out from receiving third party advertiser cookies;
  * Information on how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager06.html). 
  * Information about other third party cookies and similar technologies, including how to opt-out from receiving such third party cookies, below.

Please see the full **Cookies and Similar Technologies** section below for more information. 

How We Use Your Personal Information

Mondelēz Global uses the information we collect for many important purposes, including to: 

  * Provide the products and services you request;
  * Communicate with you regarding our products and services, as well as those of our partners and affiliates; 
  * Share or post reviews of our products and services; and
  * Display more meaningful and relevant advertisements.

How We Protect Your Information

Mondelēz Global maintains administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to protect your personal information. 

Choice & Control Over Your Personal Information

To change how Mondelēz Global contacts you, to correct or change your information or to cancel your registration with us, you can either update your information in the Your Profile section of our sites or email our Online Team using the form found at the following [page](http://mdlz.custhelp.com/app/contact/sa/1/). 

Your California Privacy Rights

Mondelēz Global may share your personal information with affiliated third parties, some of which do not share the Mondelēz name, for their own direct marketing purposes. If you would like to learn more about the types of personal information we share and who we share it with, write to us at:

Mondelēz Global LLC • 100 Deforest Avenue • East Hanover, NJ 07936 • Attention: Legal Department. 

Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy

Mondelēz Global’s sites are intended for general audiences and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 on our sites. 

Other Information

#### Links to Other Sites

  * Mondelēz Global tries to make sure that any links on our sites send you to a helpful and reliable place on the Internet, but we are not responsible for the content of these other sites or their privacy practices. 

#### Public Forums & Reviews

  * You may use our sites to post reviews of our products and services, but once you do, it becomes public information and we may continue to display your content even if you terminate your account. 

Updates to Our Privacy Statement

Check this privacy statement from time to time, as we may change or update portions of this statement at any time and without prior notice to you. 

Information We Collect

#### Information You Provide

At our sites, we collect information from you when you choose to share it with us to use our sites or services, register with our sites, sign up for newsletters or our e-mail list, sign up to receive text message alerts, participate in an online or text message survey or promotion, purchase products or services from us, or otherwise contact us. The information we collect may include your name, address, telephone number, mobile telephone number, e-mail address, age, gender, photo/image, credit/debit card number or other financial information (for example, if you make a purchase on our sites), and any other information requested at the time of collection. You may also be required to provide certain information to create an online account. While some information is mandatory to create your account, you can control what information is available to other members on our sites. We do not require you to register or provide this information to us in order to view our sites or have access to most site content. 

#### Information Collected Automatically

We may use cookies, pixel tags, server logs, and similar technologies to collect certain information about your computer or device and how you engage with our sites and ads for the purposes described in the **Cookies and Similar Technologies** section below, including to deliver online advertisements that we think would be more relevant to your interests, and to monitor interactions with our sites, emails, text messages and online advertisements. You can read more in the **Cookies and Similar Technologies** section below about the types of information we collect automatically, the technologies used to collect such information, how this information is used, and the choices you have regarding the collection and use of this information. 

#### Information Collected from Other Sources

We may obtain information about you or your device from other sources, including commercially available sources, such as data aggregators and public databases. This information may include name, demographic information, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media and shopping behavior. 

#### Combination of Information

We may combine the information we receive from and about you and your device, including personal and non-identified information collected through our sites, to help us tailor our communications to you, to improve our sites, services and products, and for all other purposes described in this privacy statement. 

#### Information Collected Automatically by Our Partners

We also may use approved third party online service providers, such as ad networks and analytics providers, to deliver, track and measure advertisements on our sites and third party websites and to assist us with other legitimate business purposes (as described in the **Cookies and Similar Technologies** section below). These providers use cookies and similar technologies when they advertise on our sites and third party websites, which may allow these providers to automatically collect non-identified information, such as your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our sites, and whether you have Flash installed. Some of these advertising providers also may use data, such as demographic data and identifiable data, received from third parties to assist in the delivery of advertisements to you. Please see the **Cookies and Similar Technologies** section below for more information. 

Cookies and Similar Technologies

When you view or interact with our sites, electronic communications and online advertisements (collectively, "sites and ads"), we automatically receive and store certain information about your computer or device and how you engage with our sites and ads. 

**Types of Information Collected Automatically**

When you view or interact with our sites and ads, we may automatically receive certain information. This information includes: 

  * Log information. Log information refers to information that is automatically sent by your web browser or device (or otherwise automatically collected by us) each time you view or interact with our sites and ads. Log information may include the site requested (for example, the MondelezInternational.com website); date and time of your request; referring URL (i.e., the website you came from); your device's IP address; location data derived from your device's IP address; browser type; browser language; device operating system; device hardware and other characteristics; device event information (for example, crash data); information regarding your use of our sites (for example, pages viewed, features used, number of clicks, time spent on a particular page); data contained in cookies; and related device and usage data. Log information is automatically recorded by our servers each time you view or interact with our sites and ads.

  * Device information. Device information refers to device-specific information that we automatically collect when you view or interact with our sites and ads. Device information may include your device type and model; device operating system and version; unique device and advertising identifiers; mobile network information; and related device information. To learn more about the information your device may make available to us, please check the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider.

  * Cookie data. Cookie data refers to the small text file(s) that are sent to or read by our servers when you view or interact with our sites and ads. Cookie data may include user preferences and other information.

  * Local storage data. Local storage data refers to data stored locally on your browser or device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (for example, HTML 5, Flash) and application data caches (i.e., a data repository on a device used for storing data locally in connection with a particular application). As with cookie data, local storage data may be sent back to or read by our servers when you view or interact with our sites and ads.

  * Statistical identifiers. Statistical identifiers refer to identifiers created using your device information and certain log information. This information, collectively, makes your web browser or device sufficiently distinct for our servers or similar systems to reasonably determine that they are encountering the same browser or device over time. Statistical identifiers enable us to uniquely identify your web browser or device for the same purposes as cookies.

In this privacy statement, the information described above is collectively referred to as "device and usage data." 

**Overview of Cookies and Similar Technologies**

We use various technologies to collect device and usage data, including cookies and similar technologies. 

  * Cookies. Cookies are small text files that are sent to and stored by your browser or device when you view or interact with our sites and ads. These cookies are then sent back unchanged to us each time you view or interact with our sites and ads in order for us to recognize your web browser or device. Cookies are used by us for a number of legitimate purposes, such as authenticating users; session tracking and storing information about specific users (for example, website preferences, buying habits); analyzing traffic to our sites; tracking the number and frequency of ads that have been shown to specific browsers or devices; and related purposes.
  
There are different types of cookies. Cookies served by the entity that operates the website you are using or viewing are called first party cookies (for example, cookies served by Mondelēz Global when you view or interact with our sites are first party cookies). Cookies served by entities that are not operating the website you are viewing or interacting with are called third party cookies (for example, cookies served by our online service providers when you use or view our sites, such as Google Analytics cookies, are third party cookies). Cookies may also endure for different periods of time. Session cookies only last as long as your web browser is open, and are deleted automatically once you close your browser. Other cookies are persistent cookies, meaning they survive after your browser is closed (for example, to recognize your browser or device when you revisit our sites). 
  * Pixel tags. Pixel tags (also called web beacons, clear GIFs and action tags) are small blocks of code installed on our sites and ads for a number of legitimate purposes, such as to allow us to track activity on our sites (for example, when e-mails are opened or content is viewed); to allow our online service providers to serve cookies on our sites and receive relevant device and usage data; and other purposes relating to the monitoring and analysis of the use and performance of our sites and ads.

  * Local storage. Local storage refers generally to the storage of data locally on your browser or device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (for example, HTML 5, Flash) and application data caches.

  * Software Development Kits. Software development kits (also called SDKs) function like third party cookies and pixel tags, but operate in the mobile app context where cookies and pixel tags cannot function as effectively. Instead, we may install pieces of code (the SDK) provided by our online service providers (for example, third party advertising companies, ad networks and analytics providers) in our mobile apps in order for our online service providers to collect and analyze relevant device and usage data.

  * Server logs. Server logs refer to the servers used by us to receive and store device and usage data.

In this privacy statement, the cookies and other technologies described above are collectively referred to as "cookies and similar technologies." For more information about cookies and similar technologies generally, please visit [ here](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

**Purposes and Uses of Cookies and Similar Technologies**

Cookies and similar technologies allow us and our online service providers to collect and track device and usage data. The following table identifies and describes the different types of cookies and similar technologies used with our sites and ads, and why we use them. 

Cookie Types | Purposes and Uses  
---|---  
**Operations & System Management** | Our sites utilize first- and third-party cookies and similar technologies that are necessary in order to operate our business and manage our sites and other systems, including authenticating and verifying users of our sites; preventing fraud and securing our sites; protecting intellectual property rights; fulfilling product and service orders, and delivering and billing for such products and services; complying with applicable laws and industry standards; and protecting our business and the safety of others.  
**Features & User Preferences** | Our sites utilize first- and third-party cookies and similar technologies to provide enhanced features and remember user preferences on our sites and ads, including identifying return users when visiting our sites (for example, to prefill fields); keeping track of user preferences, interests and past items viewed or utilized (for example, preferred language, saved items); and providing social plugins that allow users to interact with social media services (for example, Facebook, Twitter) via our sites.  
**Analytics, Product Development & Market Research** | Our sites utilize first- and third-party cookies and similar technologies for analytics, product development and market research purposes, including analyzing how individuals arrive at and engage with our sites and ads; tracking and measuring the performance and effectiveness of our sites and ads; optimizing the location of ads, features and other content on our sites and third party websites; statistical reporting in connection with activity on our sites and ads; analyzing user preferences and behaviors, and market characteristics and trends, in order to develop and improve our products, sites and ads; segmenting audiences to test features of our sites and ads; and conducting research about our consumers, products and sites.  
**Advertising & Targeting** | Our sites utilize first- and third-party cookies and similar technologies to deliver, track and measure ads both on and off our sites, including ads relevant to your interests (for example, ads based on your past interaction with our sites, ads based on predictions about your interests derived from your activities on different websites over time); and ads based on your location, demographics, or computer or device characteristics. This includes tracking and measuring the reach and frequency of ads, and regulating the delivery of such ads (for example, capping the number of times you see a particular ad). For example, we may use cookies and similar technologies to deliver relevant ads based on your location; or to group users that share a common interest into audience segments and deliver ads that may be of interest to users within a given segment; or to deliver our ads on third-party websites through a common form of online advertising known as "retargeting" or "remarketing." Retargeting works by serving ads on one website based on an individual's activities on a different website (for example, if you view a product on our site, such as Oreo® cookies, you may later see ads for Oreo® cookies when you visit a third-party website). To do this, we allow our online service providers, such as advertising agencies and ad networks, to place their own third-party cookies when users view or interact with our sites, allowing these online service providers to recognize users who have previously visited our sites. When these users visit a third-party website that includes features provided by our online service providers (for example, where our online service providers have purchased ad space), these online service providers can then recognize the users' interest in our products and services and deliver one of our ads on the third-party website.  
  
**Collection and Use of Device and Usage Data by Our Online Service Providers**

Some of our online service providers may use third-party cookies and similar technologies on unaffiliated websites and apps that include features provided by these online service providers, or unaffiliated websites and apps where these online service providers have purchased ad space. These online service providers may combine device and usage data collected through our sites and ads with device and usage data collected on unaffiliated websites and apps, and any other data maintained by such online service providers (including identifiable data), for the purposes described above and as otherwise set forth in this privacy statement. Please note that this privacy statement applies only to information collected by our online service providers through our sites and ads, and information shared with us by our online service providers. All other information collected or obtained outside our sites and ads by our online service providers is subject to the privacy practices and policies of the respective online service providers. Please refer to their websites' privacy and data sharing statements for more information. 

Subject to our approval, we may allow our online service providers to collect non-identified (i.e., device and usage data that does not identify a specific individual) or aggregated device and usage data through our sites and ads for their own legitimate business purposes. Please refer to our online service providers' privacy and data sharing statements found on their respective websites for more information regarding their collection and use of non-identified and aggregated data. 

**Your Choices**

Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. However, browsers typically allow individuals to remove or block browser cookies if they choose. For more information on blocking and removing browser cookies, please click on the relevant browser below: 

Please note that removing or blocking browser cookies does not necessarily affect third party Flash cookies which we may utilize. To delete or disable Flash cookies, please see [here](https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html?_ga=1.180001447.265154327.1459868723) for more information. 

In addition to removing and blocking browser cookies generally, the following opt-out mechanisms may also be available (note, the cookies and similar technologies identified below are subject to change at any time, and not all sites and ads utilize such cookies and similar technologies): 

  * Google Analytics. Some of our sites may use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google. Google Analytics utilizes cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze non-identified information (i.e., data that does not identify a specific individual) about the performance and use of our sites and ads. More information on Google Analytics can be found [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). If you would like to opt-out of having your information collected and used by us and our online service providers as described herein, please use the Google Analytics opt-out available [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

  * Google Retargeting. Some of our sites may use Google's Remarketing with Google Analytics to allow Google to use non-identified information (i.e., data that does not identify a specific individual) about your visits to our sites and other third-party websites in order to measure advertising effectiveness and provide ads about our goods and services that may be of interest to you. Google places its own cookies when individuals visit our sites that enable Google to recognize individuals who have previously visited our sites. When these individuals visit a third-party website on which Google has ad space, Google can then recognize these individuals' interest in our products and services and deliver one of our ads. More information on Google's Remarketing with Google Analytics can be found [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/ads/). If you would like to opt-out of having your information collected and used by us and our online service providers as described herein, please use the Google Analytics opt-out available [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

  * Adobe Analytics. Some of our sites may use Adobe Analytics provided by Adobe Systems. Adobe Analytics uses cookies and similar technologies to create reports about the use of our sites, such as which links are most used, how individuals find our sites, and whether our sites are running efficiently. If you would like to opt-out of having your information collected and used by us and our online service providers as described herein, please visit the Adobe Analytics opt-out site [here](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html).

  * Facebook Custom Audiences. Some of our sites may use Facebook Custom Audiences to deliver ads on Facebook about our products and services that may be of interest to you. More information on Facebook Custom Audiences can be found [here](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/ads-for-websites/website-custom-audiences/getting-started). If you would like to opt-out of having your information collected and used by us and our online service providers as described herein, please use the opt-out available [](http://www.aboutads.info/choices)here.

  * Interest-Based Advertising. Some of our sites may use first- and third-party cookies and similar technologies for "interest-based advertising" (targeted advertising based on web viewing data collected from a particular device over time and across unaffiliated websites - also known as online behavioral advertising) and other related purposes. If you would like to opt-out of having your information collected and used by us and our online service providers as described herein, please visit [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) or [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) if you are in the United States; or [here](http://youronlinechoices.eu/) if you are in Europe; or [here](http://youradchoices.ca/choices/) if you are in Canada.

  * Mobile Apps. For cookies and similar technologies used on our mobile apps for applicable targeted advertising activities, please follow the steps below to opt-out of having your information collected and used by us and our online service providers as described (unless different instructions are provided by your mobile device manufacturer):   
iOS Users: Launch "Settings" > Tap on "Privacy" and scroll down and tap on "Advertising" > Toggle on "Limit Ad Tracking." You can also reset your Advertising Identifier from here by tapping "Reset Advertising Identifier."   
Android Users: Open your app drawer and launch the Google Setting app > Tap "Ads" under Services and enable the "Opt out of interest-based ads" option. You can also reset your advertising ID from here by tapping "Reset advertising ID." 

Please note, disabling, removing or blocking cookies may turn off some of the features of our sites that make your experience more efficient, and some sites may not function properly. Further, if you opt-out of having your information collected and used by us and our online service providers for interest-based advertising purposes, you will continue to receive ads, but such ads will not be tailored to your specific interests based on web viewing data collected from your device over time and across unaffiliated websites. 

**Web Browser Do Not Track (DNT) Headers**

Some web browsers may transmit "do-not-track" signals to websites with which the browser communicates. Our sites do not currently respond to such "do-not-track" signals. 

**Social Media Plugins**

Our sites may use social media plugins (for example, the Facebook "Like" button, "Share to Twitter" button, "Google+" button) to enable you to easily interact with certain social media websites (for example, Facebook, Twitter, Google+, LinkedIn) and share information with others. When you visit our sites, the operators of the available social media plugins can place a cookie on your device enabling such operators to recognize individuals who have previously visited our sites. If you are logged into these social media websites while visiting our sites, the social media plugins allow the relevant social media websites to receive information that you have visited our sites or other information. The social media plugins also allow the applicable social media websites to share information about your activities on our sites with other users of the social media website. For example, Facebook Social Plugins allow Facebook to show your "Likes" and comments on our sites to your Facebook friends. Facebook Social Plugins also allow you to see your friends' Facebook activity on our sites. We do not control any of the content from the social media plugins. For more information about social media plugins from other social media websites, please refer to those websites' privacy and data sharing statements. 

How We Use Your Personal Information

Mondelēz Global may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: 

  * To respond to your questions or comments, fulfill orders, process payments and prevent transactional fraud, provide services, and contact and communicate with you; 
  * To provide you with customized sites content, targeted offers, and advertising on our sites, on other sites, or via email or text message; 
  * To contact you with information, newsletters, and promotional materials from Mondelēz Global or on behalf of our partners and affiliates; 
  * To post review of products and services on our sites;
  * To develop new products or services;
  * To address problems and review the usage and operations of our sites or business and improve our content, products, and services; 
  * To manage our telecommunications networks;
  * To protect the security or integrity of our sites and our business; and
  * As described to you at the point of data collection. 

How We Protect Your Information

Protecting your personal information is important to us. We maintain administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to help protect against unauthorized use, disclosure, alteration, or destruction of the personally identifiable information we collect on our sites. 

Choice & Control Over Your Personal Information

You are ultimately in control of the personal information you provide to us on our sites. For example, you can change your preference for follow-up contacts by e-mailing the Online Team at the address found at the paged linked to below or by changing the information in the Your Profile (or similar) section of our sites. If you prefer, you can cancel your registration and we will take steps to remove your personal information from our database. E-mail the Online team using the form at the page linked to below if you wish to take this action: [ Consumer Response Email ](http://mdlz.custhelp.com/app/contact/sa/1/)

Your California Privacy Rights

For California Residents Only. We may share your personally-identifiable information with affiliated third parties, some of which do not share the Mondelēz Global name, for their own direct marketing purposes. If you would like to learn more about the types of personal information we share with these affiliated third parties for their own direct marketing purposes, or their identities, please send a letter with your name, postal address, and e-mail, with the heading “California Privacy Rights” to: 

Mondelēz Global LLC • 100 Deforest Avenue • East Hanover, NJ 07936 • Attention: Legal Department 

Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy

Our sites are intended for general audiences and Mondelēz Global does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 on our sites. We might permit a child to send us an e-mail. We will respond to or deliver these e-mails, but we do not store the names, e-mail addresses, or the e-mails themselves in our operational database. We do not maintain this information, nor do we share it with third parties (other than support service companies as described above).

Under federal law, websites directed to children under 13 are prohibited from conditioning a child's participation in an activity on the child's disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to engage in the activity. We comply fully with this requirement. 

Upon proper identification, any parent can review any personal information we have collected from their child, if we are still maintaining the information in our operational database. They may also request that the information be deleted from our database, and refuse to permit further collection or use of their child's information. If you are a parent and wish to exercise these rights, please contact the Online Team as described below. 

Other Information

#### Links to Other Sites

Mondelēz Global reasonably tries to make sure that every link on our sites sends you to a helpful place on the Internet. We provide these links solely for your convenience and information. In addition, different websites have different privacy statements associated with the use of those sites. Please check the privacy statement of the specific site you're visiting to understand the privacy practices associated with that site. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of third party websites. 

#### Public Forums & Reviews

You may use our sites to post reviews of products and services. Any information, such as reviews, that you may disclose to your network of connections on our sites, in blogs, on message boards, in chat rooms, or on other public areas on our sites, becomes public information. Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these public areas. If you terminate your account, we may continue to show some of your content in anonymized form. 

Updates to Our Privacy Statement

We may change or update portions of this privacy statement at any time and without prior notice to you. Please check back from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates to the privacy statement. We will indicate the privacy statement’s effective date on the first page of the privacy statement.
